let questions = [{
  "numb": 1,
  "question": "Importance value varies from",
  "answer": "0 to 300",
  "options": [
    "0 to 10",
    "0 to 50",
    "0 to 100",
    "0 to 300"
  ]
},

{
  "numb": 2,
  "question": "A species found most frequently in a particular community, but also present occasionally in others is called",
  "answer": "selective species",
  "options": [
    "accidental species",
    "indifferent species",
    "selective species",
    "exclusive species"
  ]
},

{
  "numb": 3,
  "question": "Which of these depicts correctly the lithosere primary succession?",
  "answer": "rock --> crustose lichen --> foliose lichen --> moss --> herbaceous stage --> shrub --> woodland --> climax",
  "options": [
    "rock --> foliose lichen --> crustose lichen --> moss --> herbaceous stage --> shrub --> woodland -> climax",
    "moss --> crustose lichen --> foliose lichen --> rock --> herbaceous stage --> shrub --> woodland --> climax",
    "rock --> crustose lichen --> foliose lichen --> shrub --> herbaceous stage --> moss --> woodland --> climax",
    "rock --> crustose lichen --> foliose lichen --> moss --> herbaceous stage --> shrub --> woodland --> climax"
  ]
} ,

{
  "numb": 4,
  "question": "Importance value can be written as",
  "answer": "relative density + relative frequency + relative dominance",
  "options": [
    "relative density + relative frequency X relative dominance",
    "relative density X relative frequency + relative dominance",
    "relative density + relative frequency + relative dominance",
    "relative density X relative frequency X relative dominance"
  ]
},

{
  "numb": 5,
  "question": "Lithosere is an example of",
  "answer": "xerosere",
  "options": [
    "hydrosere",
    "xerosere",
    "psammosere",
    "halosere"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 6,
  "question": "The climax near Tindi village is being controlled by disturbance by cattle. This is an example of",
  "answer": "disclimax",
  "options": [
    "climatic climax",
    "edaphic climax",
    "disclimax",
    "catastrophic climax"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 7,
  "question": "A climax caused by wildfires is an example of",
  "answer": "catastrophic climax",
  "options": [
    "climatic climax",
    "edaphic climax",
    "disclimax",
    "catastrophic climax"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 8,
  "question": "Which of these is correct?",
  "answer": "a or b",
  "options": [
    "fundamental niche > realised niche",
    "fundamental niche = realised niche",
    "fundamental niche < realised niche",
    "a or b"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 9,
  "question": "When compared to generalist species, specialist species have",
  "answer": "narrower niche",
  "options": [
    "narrower niche",
    "broader niche",
    "same size niche",
    "none of these"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 10,
  "question": "Which of these is not a characteristic of pioneer species",
  "answer": "large size",
  "options": [
    "ability to grow on bare rocks",
    "ability to tolerate extreme temperatures",
    "large size",
    "short life span"
  ]
}
    ]